Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur audiovisual material, 1994 -- 2006; 1995 -- 2001; MS148.002; 0.25 Linear Feet; 552 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - 28A: Arthur's substitute teacher trouble; 28B: I'm a poet, 1995 -- 1996; MS148.002.036.00027 (Case 36)
    Dialogue paused edit. Associated production files for Arthur's substitute teacher trouble can be found at MS148/001-005#00019-00025. Associated first cut for Arthur's substitute teacher trouble can be found at MS148/002-540#00001. Associated tapes for Arthur's substitute teacher trouble can be found at MS148/002-277#00002 and MS148/002-278-00002. Associated production files for I'm a poet can be found at MS148/001-005#00026-00030 and MS148/001-005#00032-00034. Associated first cut for I'm a poet can be found at MS148/002-540#00002. Associated tapes for I'm a poet can be found at MS148/002-279#00001.
  - 29A: Arthur's New Year's Eve; 29B: Poor Muffy, 1995 -- 1996; MS148.002.036.00028; Cinar (Case 36)
    Paused edit. Associated production files for Arthur's New Year's Eve can be found at MS148/001-005#00035-00042. Associated first cut for Arthur's New Year's Eve can be found at MS148/002-541#00001. Associated mix for approval for Arthur's New Year's Eve can be found at MS148/002-064#00001. Associated tape for Arthur's New Year's Eve can be found at MS148/002-281#00002. Associated production files for Poor Muffy can be found at MS148/001-005#00043-00049. Associated first cut for Poor Muffy can be found at MS148/002-541#00002. Associated mix for approval for Poor Muffy can be found at MS148/002-064#00002. Associated tapes for Poor Muffy can be found at MS148/002-275#00002 and MS148/002-276#00002.
  - 30A: Stolen bike; 30B: My club rules, 1995 -- 1996; MS148.002.036.00029 (Case 36)
    Dialogue paused edit. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00050-00063.
  - Arthur auditions, 2000 -- 2002; MS148.002.036.00030; Cinar (Case 36)
  - Sue Ellen auditions, followed by the original Sue Ellen, 2000 -- 2002; MS148.002.036.00031; Cinar (Case 36)
  - Walker Vreeland voice-overs, 1995 -- 2002; MS148.002.036.00032 (Case 36)
  - Arthur auditions, 2001-11-20; MS148.002.036.00033; Cinar (Case 36)
    CD1, B.
  - Arthur auditions, 2001-11-20; MS148.002.036.00034; Cinar (Case 36)
    CD2, B.
  - Auditions for D.W. and Brain, 2002-02-08; MS148.002.036.00035; Cinar (Case 36)
    Additional dates include 2002-02-06 and 2002-02-07. Mimi Warshaw, D.W.; James Harbour, D.W.; Elanor Noble, Brain; Wyatt Bowen, D.W.; Jesse Camacho, D.W.; Evan Smirnow, Brain.
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, 1995-11-15; MS148.002.037.00001; Cinar (Box 37)
    Offline, first cut, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-001#00059-00064.
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, 1995-11-15; MS148.002.037.00002; Cinar (Box 37)
    Offline, first cut, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-001#00065-00072.
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, 1996-02-19; MS148.002.038.00001; Cinar (Box 38)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-001#00059-00064.
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, 1996-02-19; MS148.002.038.00002; Cinar (Box 38)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-001#00065-00072.
  - 7A: Arthur babysits, 1996-02-26; MS148.002.039.00001; Cinar (Box 39)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00001-00004.
  - 7B: D.W. all wet, 1996-02-26; MS148.002.039.00002; Cinar (Box 39)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00005-00008.
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, 1996-03-08; MS148.002.040.00001; Cinar (Box 40)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00009-00016.
  - 8B: Arthur writes a story, 1996-03-08; MS148.002.040.00002; Cinar (Box 40)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00017-00018.
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, 1995-12-01; MS148.002.041.00001; Cinar (Box 41)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00009-00016.
  - 8B: Arthur writes a story, 1995-12-01; MS148.002.041.00002; Cinar (Box 41)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00017-00018.
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, 1996-01-10; MS148.002.042.00001; Cinar (Box 42)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00019-00022.
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, 1996-01-10; MS148.002.042.00002; Cinar (Box 42)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00023-00029.
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, 1996-03-18; MS148.002.043.00001; Cinar (Box 43)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00019-00022.
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, 1996-03-18; MS148.002.043.00002; Cinar (Box 43)
    Mix for approval, final online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00023-00029.
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, 1996-03-22; MS148.002.044.00001; Cinar (Box 44)
    Mix for approval, online (4 retakes missing), not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00030-00037.
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, 1996-03-22; MS148.002.044.00002; Cinar (Box 44)
    Mix for approval, online (4 retakes missing), not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00038-00042.
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, 1996-01-12; MS148.002.045.00001; Cinar (Box 45)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00030-00037.
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, 1996-01-12; MS148.002.045.00002; Cinar (Box 45)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00038-00042.
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, 1996-01-26; MS148.002.046.00001; Cinar (Box 46)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00055-00060.
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, 1996-01-26; MS148.002.046.00002; Cinar (Box 46)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00061-00065.
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, 1996-04-08; MS148.002.047.00001; Cinar (Box 47)
    Mix for approval, online (6 retakes missing), not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00055-00060.
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, 1996-04-08; MS148.002.047.00002; Cinar (Box 47)
    Mix for approval, online (6 retakes missing), not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00061-00065.
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, 1996-02-02; MS148.002.048.00001; Cinar (Box 48)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00066-00073.
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, 1996-02-02; MS148.002.048.00002; Cinar (Box 48)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00001-00007.
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, 1996-04-16; MS148.002.049.00001; Cinar (Box 49)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-002#00066-00073.
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, 1996-04-16; MS148.002.049.00002; Cinar (Box 49)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00001-00007.
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, 1996-04-22; MS148.002.050.00001; Cinar (Box 50)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00008-00014.
  - 14B: So long, Spanky, 1996-04-22; MS148.002.050.00002; Cinar (Box 50)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00015-00018.
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, 1996-02-13; MS148.002.051.00001; Cinar (Box 51)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00008-00014.
  - 14B: So long, Spanky, 1996-02-13; MS148.002.051.00002; Cinar (Box 51)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00015-00018.
  - 15A: D.W.'s snow mystery, 1996-05-14; MS148.002.052.00001 (Box 52)
    Mix corrections. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00019-00023.
  - 15B: Arthur's almost boring day, 1996-05-14; MS148.002.052.00002 (Box 52)
    Mix corrections. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00024-00029.
  - 15A: D.W.'s snow mystery, 1996-05-06; MS148.002.053.00001; Cinar (Box 53)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00019-00023.
  - 15B: Arthur's almost boring day, 1996-05-06; MS148.002.053.00002; Cinar (Box 53)
    Mix for approval, online/not color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00024-00029.
  - 15A: D.W.'s snow mystery, 1996-02-21; MS148.002.054.00001; Cinar (Box 54)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00019-00023.
  - 15B: Arthur's almost boring day, 1996-02-21; MS148.002.054.00002; Cinar (Box 54)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00024-00029.
  - 16A: Arthur's cousin catastrophe, 1996-03-06; MS148.002.055.00001; Cinar (Box 55)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00030-00039.
  - 16B: Arthur's first sleepover, 1996-03-06; MS148.002.055.00002; Cinar (Box 55)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148-001-003#00040-00043.
  - 16A: Arthur's cousin catastrophe, 1996-05-13; MS148.002.056.00001; Cinar (Box 56)
    Mix for approval, online/color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00030-00039.
  - 16B: Arthur's first sleepover, 1996-05-13; MS148.002.056.00002; Cinar (Box 56)
    Mix for approval, online/color corrected, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00040-00043.
  - 17A: D.W.'s blankie, 1996-03-25; MS148.002.057.00001; Cinar (Box 57)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00044-00051.
  - 17B: Buster's dino dilemma, 1996-03-25; MS148.002.057.00002; Cinar (Box 57)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00052-00056.
  - 19A: Buster's new friend, 1996-04-15; MS148.002.058.00001; Cinar (Box 58)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00070-00075. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00018. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-530#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-248#00002 and MS148/002-249#00002.
  - 19B: Arthur's baby, 1996-04-15; MS148.002.058.00002; Cinar (Box 58)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-003#00073 and MS148/001-004#00001-00003. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-530#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-244#00001 and MS148/002-245#00001.
  - 20A: My Dad, the garbage man, 1996-04-23; MS148.002.059.00001; Cinar (Box 59)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00004-00009.
  - 20B: Meek for a week, 1996-04-23; MS148.002.059.00002; Cinar (Box 59)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00010-00014.
  - 20B: Meek for a week, 1996-04-30; MS148.002.060.00001; Cinar (Box 60)
    Sequence, Francine's head explosion. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00010-00014.
  - 22A: D.W. gets lost, 1996-05-13; MS148.002.061.00001; Cinar (Box 61)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00025-00028. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00021. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-532#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-271#00002 and MS148/002-272#00002.
  - 22B: Arthur's lost library book, 1996-05-13; MS148.002.061.00002; Cinar (Box 61)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00029-00034. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00021. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-532#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-230#00002 and MS148/002-231#00002.
  - 23A: D.W. the copycat, 1996-05-27; MS148.002.062.00001; Cinar (Box 62)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00035-00039. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00022. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-533#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-232#00002 and MS148/002-233#00002.
  - 23B: D.W. flips, 1996-05-27; MS148.002.062.00002; Cinar (Box 62)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00040-00045. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00022. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-533#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-255#00002 and MS148/002-256#00002.
  - 24A: Sick as a dog, 1996-06-06; MS148.002.063.00001; Cinar (Box 63)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00046-00052. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00023. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-534#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-259#00002 and MS148/002-260#00002.
  - 24B: Arthur makes the team, 1996-06-06; MS148.002.063.00002; Cinar (Box 63)
    Offline, first cut, for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-004#00053-00055. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00023. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-534#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-261#00002 and MS148/002-262#00002.
  - 29A: Arthur's New Year's Eve, 1996-08-20; MS148.002.064.00001; Cinar (Box 64)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00035-00042. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00028. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-541#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/002-281#00002.
  - 29B: Poor Muffy, 1996-08-20; MS148.002.064.00002; Cinar (Box 64)
    Mix for approval, final online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00043-00049. Associated audiocassette can be found at MS148/002-036#00028. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-541#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-275#00002 and MS148/002-276#00002.
  - 30A: Stolen bike, 1996-09-05; MS148.002.065.00001; Cinar (Box 65)
    Mix for approval, online (1 retake missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00050-00056.
  - 30B: My club rules, 1996-09-05; MS148.002.065.00002; Cinar (Box 65)
    Mix for approval, online (1 retake missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00057-00063.
  - 31A: Arthur's lucky pencil, 1997-05-09; MS148.002.066.00001; Cinar (Box 66)
    Online (31 retakes missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00064-00071.
  - 31B: Night fright, 1997-05-09; MS148.002.066.00002; Cinar (Box 66)
    Online (13 retakes missing), audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00072-00079.
  - 31A: Arthur's lucky pencil, 1997-03-26; MS148.002.067.00001; Cinar (Box 67)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00064-00071.
  - 31B: Night fright, 1997-03-26; MS148.002.067.00002; Cinar (Box 67)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00072-00079.
  - 32A: Arthur's TV-free week, 1997-06-02; MS148.002.068.00001; Cinar (Box 68)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00080-00081 and MS148/001-006#00001-00005.
  - 32B: Go to your room, D.W., 1997-06-02; MS148.002.068.00002; Cinar (Box 68)
    Online (no retakes missing), mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00006-00007.
  - 32A: Arthur's TV-free week, 1997-04-18; MS148.002.069.00001; Cinar (Box 69)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-005#00080-00081 and MS148/001-006#00001-00005.
  - 32B: Go to your room, D.W., 1997-04-18; MS148.002.069.00002; Cinar (Box 69)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00006-00007.
  - 33A: Arthur's underwear, 1997-06-23; MS148.002.070.00001; Cinar (Box 70)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00008-00012.
  - 33B: D.W., the picky eater, 1997-06-23; MS148.002.070.00002; Cinar (Box 70)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00013-00017.
  - 33A: Arthur's underwear, 1997-04-23; MS148.002.071.00001; Cinar (Box 71)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00008-00012.
  - 33B: D.W., the picky eater, 1997-04-23; MS148.002.071.00002; Cinar (Box 71)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00013-00017.
  - 33A: Arthur's underwear, 1997-04-25; MS148.002.072.00001; Cinar (Box 72)
  - 33B: D.W., the picky eater, 1997-04-25; MS148.002.072.00002; Cinar (Box 72)
  - 34A: Draw!, 1997-07-01; MS148.002.073.00001; Cinar (Box 73)
    For content approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00018-00028.
  - 34B: Binky Barnes, art expert, 1997-07-01; MS148.002.073.00002; Cinar (Box 73)
    For content approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00029-00036.
  - 34A: Draw!, 1997-05-02; MS148.002.074.00001; Cinar (Box 74)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00018-00028.
  - 34B: Binky Barnes, art expert, 1997-05-02; MS148.002.074.00002; Cinar (Box 74)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00029-00036.
  - 35A: Arthur's mystery envelope, 1997-05-16; MS148.002.075.00001; Cinar (Box 75)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00037-00043.
  - 35B: Buster Baxter, cat saver, 1997-05-16; MS148.002.075.00002; Cinar (Box 75)
    Offline, first cut for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00044-00052.
  - 36A: The big blow-up, 1997-08-04; MS148.002.076.00001; Cinar (Box 76)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00053-00060.
  - 36B: Arthur vs. the piano, 1997-08-04; MS148.002.076.00002; Cinar (Box 76)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00061-00067.
  - 37A: Buster and the daredevils, 1997-08-11; MS148.002.077.00001; Cinar (Box 77)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00068-00074.
  - 37B: Francine Frensky, Olympic rider, 1997-08-11; MS148.002.077.00002; Cinar (Box 77)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00075-00079.
  - 38A: Arthur makes a movie, 1997-08-18; MS148.002.078.00001; Cinar (Box 78)
    Mix for approval, online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-006#00080-00081 and MS148/001-007#00001-00004. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-542#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-291#00001 and MS148/002-292#00001.
  - 38B: Play it again, D.W., 1997-08-18; MS148.002.078.00002; Cinar (Box 78)
    Mix for approval, online, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00005-00011. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-542#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-295#00002 and MS148/002-296#00002.
  - 40A: Lost!, 1997-09-04; MS148.002.079.00001; Cinar (Box 79)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00026-00032. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-544#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-302#00001 and MS148/002-303#00001.
  - 40B: The short, quick summer, 1997-09-04; MS148.002.079.00002; Cinar (Box 79)
    Mix for approval, audio ch1-ch2, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00033-00037. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-544#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-302#00002 and MS148/002-303#00002.
  - 41A: Arthur and the square dance, 1997-11-18; MS148.002.080.00001; Cinar (Box 80)
    Online, mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00038-00045.
  - 41B: Water and the brain, 1997-11-18; MS148.002.080.00002; Cinar (Box 80)
    Online, mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00046-00052.
  - 42A: Grandma Thora appreciation day, 1997-11-27; MS148.002.081.00001; Cinar (Box 81)
    Online (not color corrected), mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#
  - 42B: Arthur the unfunny, 1997-11-27; MS148.002.081.00002; Cinar (Box 81)
    Online (not color corrected), mix for approval, TC burn-in. Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-007#00061-00064.